https://www.greatharvest.com/company/great-harvest-privacy-info

Great Harvest Franchising, Inc. Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy explains what information that Great Harvest Franchising, Inc. (“Great Harvest”) collects on http://www.greatharvest.com/ (the “Site”), why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share this information with third parties. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on the Site and through use of the Great Harvest mobile application, and does not apply to information collected offline, including, but not limited to, information you may provide over the phone or when visiting a Great Harvest bakery or bakery cafe location. If you disagree with any part of this Privacy Policy, then please do not use any of the Great Harvest online services.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Great Harvest may collect some personal information that identifies you or relates to you as an individual. We will only collect personally identifiable information, such as your first and last name, mailing address, e-mail address, birthdate and telephone number, if you provide it voluntarily. If you are an applicant for a Great Harvest franchise and complete a franchisee application, we will collect financial information, business ownership information, occupation, and other details that you voluntarily provide through the application process. If you are a user of our internal training site, MyGH, we also collect your hire date, birthday and optional "About Me" information you choose to add to your profile.
In addition, Great Harvest may collect certain types of non-personal information such as: browser and device information/IP address, location information (when searching for a Great Harvest location near you), demographic information, and mobile usage data that may be collected through marketing activities and data analytics for the Site.
HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION
Like most web sites, this Site gathers information such as traffic patterns and usage data to help Great Harvest understand how you use the Site. We use this information to develop new services and continue to make improvements that are important to you and Great Harvest customers. Great Harvest may also use information that you provide us to respond to your requests for information and/or services, media inquiries, identifying a Great Harvest location, and sending email materials in response to requests for Great Harvest Blog subscriptions.
Great Harvest may from time to time share your information with its third party services provider, Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. You can learn more about Google Analytics and the privacy principles it employs to keep your information safe here. Great Harvest may also use your information in connection with its third party marketing software to implement and evaluate our marketing activities and programs, including user activity on this Site. This data may be collected on an individual basis, through information that you provide Great Harvest directly on this Site, or may be collected through the use of cookies, described below.
In addition to baking fresh cookies, we also use cookies to keep track of marketing campaigns and compile aggregate data about site traffic and interaction, so that Great Harvest can offer the best user experience possible and provide better tools and services for future site visits. If you prefer, you may clear your browser of existing cookies, or set your browser to refuse cookies. Your individual browser will likely provide instructions on disabling cookies. Please be aware that your experience on this Site may be affected by disabling cookies. In this case, you may still speak with a Great Harvest representative over the telephone at (800) 442-0424 or (406) 683-6842 who will be happy to assist you and answer any questions you may have. To learn more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
Additionally, Great Harvest may contract with other third party service providers to better assist us in understanding our site visitors and their behaviors. Great Harvest does not sell or rent to third parties any of the personal information that you provide us with through the Site, and only provides this information to third-parties that are performing services directly for Great Harvest. These third party service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on the Site and on Great Harvest’s behalf for any purpose other than to help us improve our business. These third party service providers may not collect or use information from the Site for their own benefit or business purposes.
Great Harvest may also share your information with affiliates, franchisees, and/or investors. In the event that any transfer or sale of some or all of Great Harvest’s business or assets occurs, we may disclose your personal information to those involved in such a transfer or sale of assets.
In the case of MyGH users, we may use employment related information for purposes related to your employment with us (if you work for Great Harvest Franchising, Inc.) or with your employer.
REWARDS PROGRAM
Great Harvest offers you the feature of earning product rewards via our Rewards program. An app may be downloaded to your phone or other device, or you may use a physical rewards card. Upon registering your account we gather the following information: First & Last Name, State, Phone number, Birthday and Email address. This information is maintained by our third party loyalty program processor, Paytronix Systems, Inc. (“Paytronix”). We use this information to administer the program and it may also be used for data analytics and targeted marketing. We do not give this information to third parties, except for Paytronix. Using you rewards card or app will provide our rewards program your purchase details. Paytronix’s privacy policy and web site terms and conditions govern all loyalty transactions. For more information on Paytronix’s privacy policy, please follow this link to Paytronix privacy statement.
GIFT CARDS
Great Harvest offers you the feature of purchasing gift cards through the Site. Purchasing a gift card will transfer you to the web site of our third party credit and gift card processor, Mercury Payment Systems, LLC (“Mercury”). All financial data is transferred directly through Mercury and is not maintained on the Site. Mercury’s privacy policy and web site terms and conditions govern all gift card purchases. For more information on Mercury’s privacy policy, please follow this link to Mercury’s privacy statement.
FRANCHISE APPLICATIONS
Information and forms available on the “Franchising” section of this Site are applicable only to prospective franchisees. Information submitted on the online form will become a part of any application for a Great Harvest franchise that you may later submit. We may disclose your personal information submitted on the form to our business units, agents, affiliates, and to other third parties as part of our consideration of your franchise application. We do not authorize any unaffiliated third parties to use your personal information for any purpose other than consideration of your application. These third party service providers may not collect or use information from the Site for their own benefit or business purposes.
If you would like to inquire about becoming a franchisee, please click here.
HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
Great Harvest works hard to protect its Site users from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure of information. In doing so, Great Harvest maintains reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. Great Harvest cannot guarantee that its security measures will be sufficient to entirely prevent security problems and it cannot guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to Great Harvest over the Internet.
PRIVACY OF CHILDREN
This Site is not directed toward children under the age of 13, and Great Harvest does not intentionally or knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. Great Harvest believes that parents and guardians should supervise their children’s online activities and consider utilizing parental control tools available to prevent children from disclosing their names, address, and other personal information online without parental permission. It is the policy of Great Harvest that visitors under 18 years of age should not submit or post anything on the Site without parental consent. Should any child under the age of 18 provide personal information, we ask that his or her parent or guardian contact Great Harvest through one of the methods listed on the Contact Us page so that we can promptly delete the child’s information from our records.
OPT-OUT AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION
You have the right to opt out of future contact from Great Harvest at any time. You may do so by using the “unsubscribe” choice at the bottom of any e-mail marketing material or Great Harvest Blog notification. Please note that by clicking “unsubscribe,” this does not delete any personal information that Great Harvest has collected about you, but only deactivates our ability to contact you.
You maintain control over the information that we have collected on the Site. By contacting us at the telephone number listed on the Contact Us page, you may request that we provide any data that we have about you (if any), make corrections to or change any data that we have collected about you, or request that we delete any such data.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
From time to time, Great Harvest may provide links on this Site to other web sites or applications. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those web sites or the content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party web site accessed by clicking on a link on our Site. We encourage users to read the privacy statements of any third party web site before proceeding to use and/or provide information on these web sites. It is your responsibility to determine when you have left this Site and entered a third party web site.
If you post certain content from this Site to Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, or any other social media account(s), the information that you post is governed by the applicable third party web site’s terms and privacy policy.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any changes to the Privacy Policy on this web page. We will also maintain prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. If at any time you feel that Great Harvest is not abiding by this Privacy Policy, contact us immediately at (800) 442-0424 or (406) 683-6842, or submit a comment here.
Our Food
Menu
Our Wheat
The Fresh Milled Flour Difference
Real Food Made Right
Nutritional Info & FAQs
Health Benefits of Whole Grains
Recipes
© 2020 Great Harvest Franchising, Inc.
